

#### Contact

**Phone:** 0988953936

Email:

ikikaeru60474@gmail.com

# Languages

Chinese – Fluent English – Basic

#### **Personal Profile Statement**

I am currently studying for a master's degree in information engineering at National Cheng Kung University.

In the past year(2019), I mainly developed communications sofeware for embedded systems and smart vanet devices. Hope to focus more on DL in CV, memory efficient inference, DL in micro-controller research topic in the future.

# **Skill Highlights**

- C/C++/python
- Tensorflow/Basic Pytorch
- Embedded system
- Deep learning
- Communication program(TCP/IP,UDP,HTTP)
- FreeRTOS

## **Experience**

- Sensing-Seed: Design and develop embedded devices that can be used to detect hillside slippage and report instantly. (2020/03 - Present)
- AICUP Irwin (愛文) Mango Image Recognition Competition top 15% rank (2020/03 - 2020/07)
- Development of the Middleware/communication layer of smart Roadside Unit (sRSU) in VANET project. (2019/09 - 2020/06)
- Development of On-Board-Unit (OBU) to work with sRSU in VANET project (2019/09 - 2020/03)
- LUNA-16 Lung Nodule Analysis challenge (2019/10 2020/01)
- Operating System course teaching assistant (2019/09 2020/01)

## **Education**

BS Degree: Computer Science and Information Engineering – 2014 -2018 National Cheng Kung University, TW

MS Degree: **Computer Science and Information Engineering** – 2019 - present **National Cheng Kung University**, TW

### **Miscellaneous**

Github: <a href="https://github.com/murumura?tab=repositories">https://github.com/murumura?tab=repositories</a>